Jhal
's hello friends welcome to
your own YouTube channel Dharma here we
talk about weight loss. Before starting the
results of Meghna Lipta General Insurance Company,
you all must
hit the subscribe button, so let's start,
you can see your subscribers,
here what the company has posted, it has been
told that the company has openly discussed it on its channel division of
which is a good
thing,
next Amazon in the last, which I
live on the border, this crazy statement from the result is the
most important, so
you can see here that the
cross-post which the company has posted in the quarter for
and the rich source scam
company's zone president doctor came and the
weight was more and in the last it came 308
to 31.38 crore rupees, if we compare the water for with
last year, then it has
increased by an additional percentage of I don't care, so the
amount of asbestos, if we complete the water for with
water three, then it has
fallen by 15 percent at the front end, it has come down to
almost 53597  It has come here,
you will see that it is a little less than here
properly, next we will see the
total income of the company in the quarter fourth
and it is more than 300, which was the
last quarter method,
Rajan at Rs 58.61 crore
in the last year, in 2015 it was Rs 50 crore, if we
see here, if we compare the profit with the last year, then
it has increased by 22%,
that is Ram Rs 615.6 crore, if we
compare the quarter fourth with water three, then
it has increased by almost 14 percent,
that is Arun Rs 3148 crore,
next we will see the profit after tax
officer, which is the profit update, that is
Rs 348.560 crore, which was in glass water three,
hair cutting 153 crore teaspoon, which
was in the last year Rs 2193 crore, if we
compare water fourth with the last year, then
it has increased by almost anti three percent,
that is almost  63.75 crore rupees
and if we look at the quarter to fourth quarter again, then it has
increased by
almost 32.50 crore rupees. You can see that the
profit of the company here was generated
with the money from Arun Union and on the basis of turn-off,
which is a good thing.
Next, we will see the
shape of the company on GPS. It is like a waterfall, it is
easily 1.6 ₹1 touch. Now, the
quarter is ok at 60 and last year's
60 shares on this. If you look at this also, then
it has increased with the money from this hair oil
and also on the basis of tomatoes. So,
we can say here that the company has
posted very good results. So this is the entire
result of 2012. If you want, you
can read it completely. I will give it in the description box of this video film. So,
you should definitely have it in it. There might be a section in it on Monday.
You have to pay
attention to this. To get such updates,
subscribe to our channel and
hit the red button given nearby so that
you will get the upcoming updates.  First to know thank
you thanks for watching the